I'm sorry, Guli.
I really don't want to marry that prince.
When you wake up,
find a good way out for yourself.
Oh, True God, please grant me a way to salvation.
The princess ran away from her wedding.
How should I explain this to my king?
What should I do?
Miss, are you alright?
Miss.
Whose daughter is this? Miss?
Such a beautiful girl.
She can almost rival our Princess Xiyao.
Princess, you're awake.
What did you call me?
Princess.
You are the brightest pearl of Rouran,
Princess Xiyao.
You had a high fever for months.
You just got your energy back.
It's normal to forget things.
Have a good rest, Princess.
In a few days,
you will have a grand wedding
and marry Prince Yu of our Heavenly Kingdom.
Prince Yu? Yes.
So this is the princess.
The princess is so beautiful.
The bride is so beautiful.
Look.
So beautiful. The prince is handsome too.
What a handsome couple.
As expected of the Princess of Rouran.
A match made in heaven.
I'm so jealous.
They are truly meant for each other.
The princess and the prince make a beautiful tale.
How wonderful. They are a perfect match.
What a perfect match.
I have come out of the city to welcome the bride according to Rouran etiquette.
Why don't I see the bride?
This is Princess Xiyao.
Could it be Uncle's arrangement?
In that case,
please.
Zhiluo.
Prince Yu, this...
Men,
return to the mansion.
Get some good rest first.
The imperial physician will be here shortly.
What did you just say my name was?
Tang Zhiluo.
Your name is Tang Zhiluo.
You are my fiancée.
Tang Zhiluo, such a familiar name.
But why can't I remember anything?
You are like this every time.
Every time you die, it's not a real death.
Your body will disappear.
But you will reappear
in a place full of spiritual energy.
But the price...
Zhiluo.
But the price
is losing all your memories.
Sir.
I only lost my memory,
not my mind.
What you said is too unbelievable.
Why should I believe you?
I know I'm not a real princess.
But this resurrection you mentioned is too...
I know it's hard for you to believe this right now.
But there is one thing that can prove my words.
On your arm,
is there a birthmark?
Something even I don't know,
how does he know?
Zhiluo.
It's all because of my mistakes
that I lost you.
I don't want to lose you again this time.
Sorry, I still can't believe what you said.
As for the Soul Jade you mentioned,
if it really exists,
just take it out.
I lost it.
But I'm really not lying to you.
Every time you die, it leaves traces.
I can take you to find them.
If what you said is true,
if you truly love someone,
how could you let her die again and again?
You're right.
It's my fault.
Your Highness.
What's wrong?
Prince Yu brought an edict.
He said
he must see you and Princess Xiyao.
I see.